

CONTACT ME AT



kumgauri15@gmail.com



8237191377, 9359023055



linkedin.com/in/gaurikumbhar-32205b17a

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Creative and Technical Writing, Understanding of learning models, Conceptualizing and ideating stories, Purpose-led research
- Planning and strategizing, Organizational and monitoring skills, Proof reading and editing
- Social interaction, Excellent interpersonal and Corporate communication skills, Quick grasping, Adaptability, and a Constant learner
- Microsoft Word, Excel, Outlook, Power Point, Latex, Blogger
- Familiar with writing styles, Windows, Fedora, and Ubuntu

GAURI KUMBHAR

CONTENT WRITER

PERSONAL PROFILE

An Engineer with a pen and 2.7 years of experience in Script Writing, Content Writing & Editing. Currently looking for a job where I can bring my skills to the table, innovate, and excel in my field. A position where I can use aforementioned skill-set to implement the needs of my organization and enhance my knowledge base.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content Writer and Executive

Advids Intesome Solutions | Aug 2018 - Oct 2019

- Creative and technical script writing
- Responsible for successful deliveries of 30+ live videos within stipulated deadlines
- Assisted 2 team leads in Creative Director's team
- Hands on experience in directly communicating with the client to gather requirements and timely feedback
- Additionally, was a Voice coordinator for a period of 6 months

Freelance Academic Writer Content Ninja | Dec 2019 - Jan 2020

- Academic research
- Academic writing

Content Writer

Write Design Deliver Advertising | Feb 2020 - Currently Serving Notice Period

- Drafting plans and paper presentations for pitches
- Strategizing monthly social media calendars and developing content for the same + Social media ad campaigns
- Print medium advertising- brochures, newsletter, company profile
- Blog writing and website content development
- Client Communication



CONTACT ME AT



kumgauri15@gmail.com



8237191377, 9359023055



linkedin.com/in/gaurikumbhar-32205b17a

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Creative and Technical Writing, Understanding of learning models, Conceptualizing and ideating stories, Purpose-led research
- Planning and strategizing,
 Organizational and monitoring skills, Proof reading and editing
- Social interaction, Excellent interpersonal and Corporate communication skills, Quick grasping, Adaptability, and a Constant learner
- Microsoft Word, Excel, Outlook, Power Point, Latex, Blogger
- Familiar with writing styles,
 Windows, Fedora, and Ubuntu

GAURI KUMBHAR

CONTENT WRITER

EDUCATION

A.I.S.S.M.S College Of Engineering	2018
B.E Computer	66%
Sangameshwar Junior College	2014
H.S.C Science	78%
Little Flower Convent High School	2012
S.S.C	89%

INTERESTS

- Painting, dancing and travelling
- Organized and led college-scale technical events
- Anchored for cultural events

LANGUAGES

Hindi, English, Marathi, Kannada